The next thing we're going to do is we're going to stretch out our back.
So anytime you work your abs, you want to stretch your back, work your back and then stretch your back out.
So this is going to be a really great stretch for your abs and for your back.
It's a modified back bend on the ball, it feels really great on your spine.
And anybody of any age can do this.
If you need some assistance, please use somebody to help you, if you're a little nervous or if you get sick going backwards, cause sometimes that can happen too.
You want to take your feet, they're out, they're about hip width apart and you want to slowly go back, especially if you haven't done this before, rolling your butt forward, slowly come back, bring your hands down.
Some people are going to be a little more nervous than others, but eventually what you want to do is you want to get both of your hands flat on the floor, just like this, and both of your feet are flat on the floor.
Now different stability balls will give you different, different opportunities to stretch your back at different levels.
This is actually really good what I have here, I could go for a little bit of a larger stability ball, but I wanted to go for a little bit of a deeper stretch.
But for right now, this is good.
And once you've held this for about twenty to thirty seconds, you want to slowly come up, bring in your head up first, then your hands, then come back up to that seated position.
And that is a great way to stretch out your abs and your back on the stability ball.